todaysdod.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Passwird.com | Deals and Bargains

### Internet User Privacy

Your privacy is important to us.

This site respects privacy of Internet Users and does not collect personally identifying information without the Internet User's permission.

#### Collection of Data

This site collects non-personally identifiable information, for example, browser type, operating system, domain name, time spent on the web site, or referring link. This information may be used for system, website, and process improvements.

This site does not sell or rent personally identifying information. This site does not disclose personally identifying information to anyone that is not authorized to do so. This site uses anonymous user data to create and report the browsing, purchasing and/or lead form completion activities of anonymous users.

We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. We will collect and use personal information solely for fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other ancillary purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. We will only retain personal information for as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.

This site reserves the right to release information on Internet Users if compelled to do so by proper judicial or governmental authorities. Disclosure shall be limited to only to those we are compelled to disclose to. At present, all information processing occurs in the United States.

### Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites

This site contains links to other Internet websites and has no control or authority over the information submitted/collected by these third party website(s). Please refer to the respective Privacy Policy of the individual third party website(s).

### Use and Disclosure of Data

#### Spam

This site does not intentionally send unsolicited e-mail messages that could legitimately be construed as spam.

#### COPPA

This site complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. This site is not specifically directed to children under 18. If this site has been informed or unintentionally collected or received information from a child under 18, we will immediately delete such information from our databases. This site shall not knowingly distribute any personally identifiable information erroneously collected from children under 18.

### Policy Changes

With or without prior notification, passwird.com may change this privacy policy from time to time at passwird.com's sole discretion. All changes will be posted at this site. Except as otherwise required by law, modifications to this Privacy Policy will not affect the privacy of data collected by us prior to the effective date of the policy change.

### Cookie & Privacy

We use cookies, pixels and similar technologies for security purposes and to deliver products, services and advertisements, as well as to understand how these products, services and advertisements are used.

By using our site or services, you are agreeing to the use of cookies and similar technologies for the purpose we describe in this policy.

#### What is a cookie?

A cookie is a small file that is placed onto your device and that is managed by your browser. Cookies were designed for website to remember state based. For example, cookies enable us to identify your device and enable you to easily share content on our site and services and help us serve relevant ads to you.

Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information about you and therefore cannot be used to identify you personally.

#### Managing cookies:

You can set your browser to warn you about attempts to place cookies on your computer or limit the type of cookies you allow. Please note that companies delivering advertisements on our site may also use cookies or other technologies, and those practices are subject to their own policies.

To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/), or [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).
